module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What Is the airspeed velocity of an unladen swallow?',
      a: 'Top Gun',
      b: 'Monty Python and the Holy Grail',
      c: 'Die Hard',
      d: 'Karate Kid',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'For the LAST TIME we did not order a giant trampoline?',
      a: 'Bill and Ted’s Excellent Adventure',
      b: 'Aladdin',
      c: 'The Emperor\'s New Groove',
      d: 'Chicken Little',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Gee, I\'m really sorry your mom blew up, Ricky... guess she won\'t be able to eat any spicy foods for awhile.',
      a: 'Ghostbusters',
      b: 'Bottle Rocket',
      c: 'The Cannonball Run',
      d: 'Better off Dead',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Never go in against a Sicilian when DEATH is on the line!',
      a: 'Gladiator',
      b: 'Helen of Troy',
      c: '300',
      d: 'Princess Bride',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Go to your house?? In 3D land?',
      a: 'Space Jam',
      b: 'Mary Poppins',
      c: 'The SpongeBob SquarePants Movie',
      d: 'Enchanted',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'I don’t have a bandit mask but I modified this tube sock',
      a: 'Moonrise Kingdom',
      b: 'The Pink Panther',
      c: 'Fantastic Mr. Fox',
      d: 'Meet the Robinsons',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'You love Ladysmith Black Mambazo!',
      a: 'Princess Diaries ',
      b: 'Ms. Congeniality',
      c: 'The Lizzie Mcguire Movie',
      d: 'Mean Girls',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The secret ingredient is rattlesnake venom. Really makes the color pop. It’s perfectly harmless… when it’s dry.',
      a: 'My Name is Nobody',
      b: 'Holes',
      c: 'The Hateful Eight',
      d: 'Hell or Highwater',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Does it come in black?',
      a: 'Men in Black',
      b: 'Batman Begins',
      c: 'The Terminator',
      d: 'Mr. & Mrs. Smith',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'You’re an embarrassment to nature, you know that?',
      a: 'How to Train your Dragon',
      b: 'Brother Bear',
      c: 'Finding Nemo',
      d: 'Ice Age',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};